{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_N'Kono",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Cameroon",
    "human_readable": "Thomas N'Kono was born in Cameroon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.937892496585846,
            "question": "Is Thomas N'Kono Cameroonian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8738980889320374,
            "question": "Where was Thomas N'Kono born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.667059600353241,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Thomas N'Kono's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6438559889793396,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Thomas N'Kono?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6418518424034119,
            "question": "Where did Thomas N'Kono originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6214416027069092,
            "question": "Is Cameroon known for producing athletes like Thomas N'Kono?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5343263745307922,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the culture of Thomas N'Kono's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4419620633125305,
            "question": "What country is associated with Thomas N'Kono?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3637324571609497,
            "question": "In which country did Thomas N'Kono spend his early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3296988010406494,
            "question": "Besides being a famous athlete, what else is known about Thomas N'Kono's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas N'Kono was born in Cameroon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8462_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Thomas N'Kono spend his early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8462_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is associated with Thomas N'Kono?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8462_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the culture of Thomas N'Kono's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8462_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8462_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Thomas N'Kono was indeed born in Cameroon. According to document 3 and 4, he was \"born on July 20, 1956, in Dizangue, N\u2019Kono came to prominence at Canon Yaounde\", which implies that he was born in Cameroon."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Thomas N'Kono was born on July 20, 1956, in Dizangue, Cameroon, which supports the statement that he was born in Cameroon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}